# Sandy Lin

4F., No. 180, Wanda Rd., Wanhua Dist., Taipei City, Taiwan | +886-903142316 | +886-958284776 |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-1-b97150117/ b810521@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

My past experience focuses on B-to-B Service, it equips me with hands-on experience relating to project administration, service management, order management, auditing and billing domain. I provided a high-level technical support to reduce engineering workload, troubleshoot system problems to ensure the accuracy of the cash flow and mail delivery.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Business Administration** 

Yuan Ze university | September 2010 – June 2014

**Exchange Student Program** 

City University of Hong Kong | August 2013 – December 2013

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Underwriters Laboratories | Client Service Specialist Taipei, Taiwan | September 2015 - May 2021 Key Responsibilities

- Managed 53 product categories in domestic wire and cable industry.
- Assisted customers with project management and assisted local collection team to ensure accuracy
  of invoices to meet cash flow targets
- Built up new service knowledge to align with division business strategies
- Participated in trade shows and technical conferences, presented obtained knowledge and information to team or coworkers after the event
- Determined customer needs and guided them to make decisions about product certification
- Provided training to colleagues on programs and processes, technical support to in house employees
- Collaborated and coordinated with Operations, Support Services, Quality Assurance, Sales,
   Business Development and other affiliated stakeholders to ensure that clients experience superior service
- Supported global team to implement system successfully
- Classified customers, updated and maintained customer database (Internal oracle database, MyUL Product IQ, My UL Portal)
- Provided quotes, organized and processed samples for assigned client accounts

#### Key Achievement

- Achieved referral business opportunity target \$15K across division
- Met 90% of assigned myUL email campaign customer registered
- Encouraged 150+ clients to register for new platform, MyUL Portal in 2019
- Met internal KPI target (92% of Engineer Support team e-Mail responses within 24hrs & 94% of personal e-Mail responses within 24hrs in 2015~2021)
- Supported Sales to help key account customers register MyUL successfully (100%)
- Supported global team to implement system successfully, myUL Portal, Product iQ, ECM

#### Ezfly International Travel Agent Co Ltd | Wholesaler Taipei, Taiwan | March 2015 - September 2015

- Sold group tours and tour packages to retail travel agents
- Participated in travel exhibitions and sell tours to customers
- Reached highest monthly sales revenue record: NT\$ 1 million

# **Sandy Lin**

4F., No. 180, Wanda Rd., Wanhua Dist., Taipei City, Taiwan | +886-903142316 | +886-958284776 |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-1-b97150117/ b810521@gmail.com

### **LANGUAGE**

Chinese: Native English: Fluent German: Basic

## **SKILLS**

MS Office, Customer Satisfaction, Project management, Teamwork, Communication, Oracle

### **INTERESTS**

Build websites (https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/), and research Python used in business processes